ACTWU Legislative and Political Department Files 5619/033
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Trade Lobby Days, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Textile and Apparel Statistics, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- Letters to Hill, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- Japan- US Trade Information, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- Trade Bill, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 67)
- ICF Report, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 68)
- Final ICF Report, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- Monthly Trade Figures, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- Imports- Report from Gundersheim, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 71)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Facts (Box 24, Folder 72)
- Co-Sponsors of Textile Bill, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 73)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Schedule and Hand-outs for House vote (Box 24, Folder 74)
- Mailings to Field on Textile Bill, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Unfair Imports, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Mobilization, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Letters to Congress on Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Report- Congressional Research Service, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Hollings Speech Introducing Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- (Box 25, Folder 7)
  February 19
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- General Outline (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Our Basic Package (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Section Analysis (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- - FFACT Sheet (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Testimony: Jack Sheinkman, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  May
- Testimony on Trade, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  February 5
- CBI- Dear Colleague Letter, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Testimony on Trade, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Proposed Textile Legislation, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Talking Points of Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- Changes from Old Bill, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act-FFACT White Paper, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- FFACT Questions and Answers, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- FFACT Kit, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- National Consumers League Project, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Mailings from Headquarters to Field, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Pioneer`s System, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Hordis Brothers, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  newspaper clippings
- Illinois Glove Company, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Labor Department - Pacific Northwest Application, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Otis Elevator, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- California Prison Industry Board, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Andrew Pallack Company- EDA Loan, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Mario Papa and Sons Company- Investigation of a South Dakota Firm, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Uniroyal Company, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Government Contracts, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Zensen, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Films, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Handicapped Workers, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Education Information, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Health and Safety Manual, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Uniforms, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Cavalier Clothing, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Xerox- Public Policy Information from Government Affairs, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Fonda Group, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Rawlings Sporting Goods, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- OSHA Case- Glove Cities, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- ACTWU- Health, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- United Foods, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Butterwick Merger- ACTWU Case, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Electronic Banking System, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Cavalier Clothes, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Jost Fiess Company- Free Trade Zone Application, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Target Sportswear, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- ACTWU- Local Political Action, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Hanes project, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Health-Tex Closing, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Biltwell Company, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Chicago Health Care Problem, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Standard Industrial Classification, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Fulton Company Joint Sewage Treatment, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Glove City Area Joint Board, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Arbeka, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Arbeka Webbing Company Case, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Mailings to Carroll, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Brand Name Directory, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Conventions Resolution, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- ACTWU- Reports, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Democratic National Convention, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Shirley Carr, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Cesar Chavez, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Marion Wright Edelman, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Jim Hightower, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Reverend Jesse Jackson, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Lane Kirkland, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Jay Mazur, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Italians, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- ACTWU- PAC Awards, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- A (Box 26, Folder 44)
- ACTWU- Political Contributions, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- ACTWU- Resolutions, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- ACTWU- Awards, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Resolution on the Legislative Needs of Working People, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Southern Regional Joint Board, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- 1990 Convention Report (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Convention report, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- 1990 ACTWU Report (Box 27, Folder 6)
- ACTWU- Convention Display, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- ACTWU- Per Capita Records, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- ACTWU- Convention Awards, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Cosponsors of H.R. 5, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Workers Fairness Bill, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Mackay Case, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Striker Replacement Legislation, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Democratic Appointment for Delegates, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- AFL-CLO Opposition, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Clinton- Gore, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Congressional Record of 102nd Congress, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Amendment 6, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- ACTWU- Jobs, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Paying to Lose Our Jobs, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Aid to Labor, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- ACTWU- NAFTA, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Bush Administration- NAFTA, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- NAFTA- Sierra Club Center for Environmental Innovation, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Congressional Remarks on North Atlantic Free Trade Agreement, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Labor Advisory Committee on NAFTA, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- NAFTA- Industry Sectors and Geographic Regions, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Clinton- Gore, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Congressmen Waxman and Gephardt, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Fair Trade Campaign, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Saipan, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Saipan, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- The Garment Industry in the Northern Marianas, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Saipan Clothing Importers, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Saipan, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- NAFTA- Opposition, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- NAFTA- Farmworkers and Women, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- NAFTA_ Support, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- NAFTA- Southwest Region and Florida, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- NAFTA- Legislation and General Information, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- NAFTA- Citizens Analysis, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- NAFTA: AFL-CIO- Executive Board Statements and Targeted Congressional Districts, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Statements in the Committee of Insular and International Affairs, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Labor Enforcement in Saipan, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- 1992 Elections (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Delegate Selection Plan Status, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- United States` Aid (Box 29, Folder 8)
  video
- Community Reinvestment Act, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Tariff Bill, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Saipan, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Cost of Protection, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- North Atlantic Free Trade Agreement, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Tax Credits For Corporation Takeovers, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Coalition Against Double Taxation, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Moynihan Amendment, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Middle Income Tax Proposal, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Capital Gains, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Resolution to Protect US Mainland Jobs, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- School Readiness Act, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Citizens for Tax Justice Case Study, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plans, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- AFL- CIO Cope, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers` Union, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Vice President George Bush, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- House Incumbent, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- 1992 Presidential Campaign (Box 30, Folder 15)
- 1992 Campaign Candidates (Box 30, Folder 16)
- ACTWU, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- 1990 Elections (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Banking, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Wool Bill, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Zwicker, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Extended Benefits Program, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Job Site Safety, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Job Site Safety, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Comprehensive Occupational Safety and Health Reform Act, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Comprehensive Occupational Safety and Health Reform Act, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Comprehensive Occupational Safety and Health Reform Act, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Clean Air Act, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Health and Safety, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Long Term Care Campaign, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Health Care Act, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Health Care Reform, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Health Insurance, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Health Insurance, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Health Insurance, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Health Insurance, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Retail Competition Enforcement bill, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Retail Competition Act, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Trade- fast Track, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Child Labor, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Child Labor, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  clips
- TRADE- Child Labor Overseas, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Unemployment Insurance Fund, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Haitian Labor Right, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  April
- House Trade and Competitiveness Task Force, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Canon Pensions, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Wool Bill, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Wool Tariff Bill, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Tariff Suspension- fine wool fabric, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Berry Amendment, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Smooth Hawley Act, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Leslie Wexner, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Trade- China, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- China Slave Labor, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- China's prison labor, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative- Footwear and Leather Production, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Foreign Trade Zones, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Foreign Abuses, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Northern Marianas, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Maquiladora program, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Foreign Lobbyist, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Trade- Country Bilaterals, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Trade- Monthly Import Figures, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Striker Bill, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Worker`s Rights, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Political PAC Horror Stories, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Political Action Committee, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Voter Registration, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Democratic National Convention- Women`s Issues, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Federal Election Commission, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Lobbyist- Voter Registration, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Amalgamate Medicare Insured Group, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Joint Board, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- ACTWU Retirees, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  letters
- Political Funds, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Congressional Quarterly Computing System, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- AFL- CIO Legislative Alerts, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Election of 1988 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Get the Vote Out Drive, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Voter Registration- Virginia, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Voter Registration, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Senate Contributions, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Voter Registration 1984 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Voter Registration Campaign, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Politics, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Textile Caucus, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Democratic National Committee, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Delegate Selection, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- ACTWU- Lobby Materials, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- State by State House Districts, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Christmas Mailing List, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Right Wing, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Right Wing, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Children`s Defense Fund, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Campaign Spending, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- State and District Offices, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Politics, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Youth Employment Act, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Senate Campaign, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  clips from newspapers
- Fieldcrest Canon, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Cone Mills Employee Stock Ownership Plan, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Clinton and Gore Campaign, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- AID Out of Job Export, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Aid out of Jobs, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Agency for Internal Development, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Congressional Record, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  September 30
- Labor Committee- El Salvador, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Labor- Workplace, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Congressional Campaigns- 1992 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Work Issues, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Work Topics, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Work, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Research on Workplace, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Research on Workplace, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Research on Workplace, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Family and Medical Leave, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Family and Medical Leave Act, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Civil Rights, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Senate Races List, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Projects, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Committee on Political Education, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Judiciary- Crimes- Federal Prisons, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Exports, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Textile legislation, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Agriculture Trade, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Congressional State membership, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Textile Legislation, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Pension Protection Bill, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Smoot- Hawley, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Textile Bill, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Minimum Wage Bill, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Canada Free Trade Argument, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Balance Budget, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Testimony on Trade, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Textile Bill, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Textile Research, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- 1986 Trade Figures (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Textile- Wool, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act- Testimony, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Textile Bill- Cosponsors, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- Protectionism, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- Horror Stories, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- US Chamber of Commerce Report- Jobs, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- History of Unfair Trade Cases, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act-Senate Letters and Legislation, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- Foreign Money, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Neckwear Association of America, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- American Fiber, Textile, Apparel Coalition, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Trade- Negotiations with Japan, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Industrial Statistics- ACTWU Research Department, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Ladies Garment Workers` Union Statistics, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- 1986 Senate Race, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- Talking Points and Surveys, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Retail Competition Act, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Voter Registration Bill, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- FFACT Executive Members, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Textile Clothing Technology Corporation, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Footwear Association, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- Analysis, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- 101st Congress- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act-Cosponsors, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act- Congressional Contacts, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Reconciliation Legislation, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Textile Imports, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Districts, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Free Trade, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Retail Industry Trade Action Coalition, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- 1990 Trade Bill- Footwear, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Corporate Takeovers, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Berry Amendment, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Trade- Mexico, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- National Apparel Technology Center, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Textiles- Quick response, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- US Canadian Free Trade Agreement, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Minimum Wage- Testimony, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Amendment of Securities Act 1934, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Corporate Takeovers, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Industrial Homework, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Product Safety, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- 100th Congress, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Expense Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Industrial Homework, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Industrial Homework, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Smoot Hawley, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Textile and Apparel Jobs, 1986-1989 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Minimum Wage and Job Lost, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Footwear Fact Sheets, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Pensions, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Reconciliation Bill, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Opposition to Textile Bill, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Political Action- ACTWU, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act-Facts, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- ACTWU, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  Envelopes
- Coalition for Trade, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Free Enterprise Zone, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Labor Law Violators, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Universal Telephone Service Preservation Act, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Contra Vote, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Worker Ownership Act, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Corporate Takeovers, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Tax on Health Care Coverage, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Trade Protectionism, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Expo- Maquila, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Minimum Wage Legislation, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Health Care, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Trade Bill, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  articles
- High Risk Occupational Disease Notification and Prevention Act, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Minimum Wage, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Walter Lenahan, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Small Business Act, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Corporate Takeovers, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Unrelatable Business Income Tax, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Minimum Health Benefits for all Workers Act, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Lichtenberg, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 28)